

JENNIE

1901-930 6Ave SW Calgary, Alberta T2P 1J3 hj.jennie.lee@gmail.com 1-587-893-7943

Dear Hiring Manager,

Thank you for considering my application for a Software Developer in a summer intern position.

As a Software Development major student attending at Southern Alberta Institute of Technology, I am excited to apply for the Software Developer summer intern position where I may contribute my academic learning to bring improvement to future and existing programs.

Through the Software Development curriculum, I gained technical experience in a wide range of information technology topics such as object-oriented programming using languages Java and user interface, computer graphic, and web design using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. My past dynamic experiences have prepared me with the knowledge and skills needed to be an exceptional employee. I bring 4 years of experience and knowledge on design and art theory as I hold a Fine Arts bachelor's degree as well as have taken the course of Media Arts. I am an expert in graphic design software such as Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Premiere as well as Microsoft office suites. In the past, I produced graphic design content and managed social media channels and websites for the Korean Consulate General, Trade and Investment office in Toronto.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I hope you will find my knowledge and experience a great potential. As a Software Developer, my goal is to continually develop technical programming skills in order to present better solutions to assist my employers and their clients to achieve their goals. I would greatly appreciate the opportunity to further discuss how I can support the purpose of helping clients thrive and communities prosper through this Software Developer summer intern position. Please contact me at 587-893-7943 or hj.jennie.lee@gmail.com I am available for 4, and 8month internship positions starting this May.

Jennie Hyunju Le	_

Sincerely,

JENNIE HYUNJU LEE

PROFILE

After 5 years experience in the **design industry**, and now studying **IT software development** to combine.

A vibrant, punctual, and organized individual person who pays attention to detail, advocates for the community.

Analytical to the interpersonal relationships while inviting peers to open dialogue through non-judgemental discussions. Has a positive and enthusiastic personality. Thrives in professional environments that allow room for creativity.

CONTACT

- +1 587 893 7943
- hj.jennie.lee@gmail.com
- n 930 6 Ave SW Calgary, AB
- jennielee.netlify.app
- github.com/JenHLee
- dribbble.com/JenHLee

EDUCATION

- The Southern Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT)
 IT-Software Development
 3.94/4.0 GPA
 Calgary, Canada
 Class of 2023 (Expected)
 - Kyunghee University
 Seoul, Korea
 Majoring in Fine Art & Media Art
 3.743/4.3 GPA
 Graduated at the second-highest GPA
 in a graduating class
- Goyang High School of Arts Goyang, Korea
 Majoring in Fine Art

Class of 2011

Class of 2015

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

- ◆ Language | Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- SVC | Github, Git
- IDE | Visual Studio, Eclipse, BlueJ
- OS | Window, Mac

DESIGN SKILLS

- Sketch
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Premiere

GENERAL SKILLS

- Expert in Microsoft Office suites
- Write well-designed, testable code
- Problem-solving skills
- Excellent time management skills

LANGUAGES & OTHER INTERESTS

- Fluent in Korean
- Vice-President of SSC(Sharing Showing your Code)
 Mentoring Club at SAIT
- Volunteering as a Tech Mentor at Calgary Public Library | to library patrons with computer skills; use of the Internet, software applications, coding, social media, and mobile devices.

EXPERIENCES | PERSONAL PROJECT

Spacestagram | Web Application Astronomy Picture of the Day Demo | spacestagram-nasa-api.netlify.app

Github | github.com/JenHLee/Shopify-Nasa-Challenge

HTML + CSS + JavaScript + NASA API

- Fetches from NASA's Astronomy Picture of the Day API.
- Image-sharing website application for Shopify winter 2022 frontend developer internship.
- · Load 5 images at that time.
- · Starfield background animation can control the speed.

Vanila ToDo-List | Web Application

Demo | jentodolist.netlify.app

Github | github.com/JenHLee/ToDoList

HTML + CSS + JavaScript

- · Animated interactions with UI components.
- All, Completed, and Uncompleted.
- Using vanilla JavaScript, make the web application faster than jQuery.

Jennie's Portfolio Website

Demo | jennielee.netlify.app

Github | github.com/JenHLee/Website

HTML + CSS + JavaScript + Swiper

- Create modern, responsive sliders on the website using SwiperJS.
- Change theme of the responsive website on button click.
- Using media query to responsive the website to all devices.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Daniel School in North YorkToronto, Canada

Oct.2018 - Jun.2019

Art Instructor

- Teaching a classroom of Elementary students from Grade 1-4 weekly paying close attention to each student.
- Guiding them to discover a passion for art and to assist their creative expression through various mediums and techniques.
- Evaluating students' performance and growth in art and writing progress reports.

KOTRA

Trade-Investment Promotion Agency of Korea Consulate Toronto, Canada

Oct.2018 - Jun.2019

Intern | Marketing & Graphic Design

- Created content for managing KotraOmni website (Shopify) and Social Media Services.
- Performed administrative duties and marketing tasks, giving support in daily needs and managing general activities, assisting marketing manager.
- Took part in the organizing of the 'K-beauty in Montreal 2018' event.
- · Translated Korean and English documents.

Womanstalk (E-Commerce) Seoul, Korea

Jan.2018 - Jul.2018

Korea Research Institute for Traditional Lanterns Yangju, Korea

Feb.2015 - Jun.2018

Marketer & Graphic Designer

- Created graphic design contents of K-beauty used by Adobe software.
- Managed Social Media Services (Instagram, Facebook, and Youtube.)

Graphic Designer

- Managed the project 'Seoul Lantern Festival'.
- Developed traditional lantern designs, mocked up the files.
- · Produced the works.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

- CJ Olive Young Botanic Healboh Seoul, Korea
- BonDavinch Museum

Seoul. Korea

Dr.medicean
 Seoul, Korea

- Created digital content, associated with the Creative manager to create video content using Adobe Premiere as an ambassador in CJ Oliveyoung BotanicHealboh, Cosmetic Brand.
- Work with the marketing team to shape messaging and concepts of cosmetic products.
- Created digital content and managed Social Media Services for the "Oscar-Claude Monet exhibition" as an ambassador in BonDavinch Museum.
- Covering exhibition and events.
- Created digital content and managed Social Media Services as an ambassador in Dr.medicean Cosmetic Brands
- Reviewed cosmetic products.

REFERENCES

Jungsu Abraham Sohn

Linux Software Developer | Siemens | Calgary, Canada jungsu.sohn@siemens.com

Kelvin Lee

Assistant Deputy Director | KOTRA Toronto (Consulate General Of The Republic Of Korea-Commercial Section)
Toronto, Canada
kelvin.lee@kotra.ca | +1 416 368 3399(214)

Kate Jung

Entrepreneurship Coordinator | City of Vaughan | Vaughan, Canada kate.jung@vaughan.ca | +1 647 463 9188